Hariprasad Poojary Web Developer

- Mangalore, India
- +917208551923
- in Hariprasad Poojary

- haridx.poojary@gmail.com
- **# 18 Jun 1995**
- HariprasadPoojary



PROFILE

Around 4+ years of IT experience with Tech Mahindra. My technical skills are majorly in Software Testing and Web Development. Decent domain knowledge in the Telecom industry.

Over 1+ years of experience in web application development using Python, Django, and other web technologies.

Working in a variety of test phases like system test, system integration test, E2E test. Scripting in Python, PL/SQL to automate the test.

Have very good analytical, communication skills, able to deal with complicated projects, ability to understand complex designs, and creating high quality and timely working results.

G-7

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Tech Mahindra LTD

Aug 2020 – present India

Software Engineer

- Experience in gathering requirements by attending several meetings.
- Created templates for page rendering and Django views for the business logic.
- Used Django REST framework and integrated new and existing API endpoints.
- Created forms and loaded data into the Oracle/Postgres database.

Dec 2017 - Aug 2020 Hague, Netherlands

Software Engineer

Client Location/Onsite Role:

- Developed scripts to automate tests in Python and PL\SQL
- Worked on web-based applications using Python, Django, CSS3, HTML5, JavaScript
- Managing UAT Demo and Test support

2016 – 2017 Pune, India

Software Engineer

- Client KPN, Netherlands
- Domain Landline and Mobile telecommunications
- Project Complete OSS transformation with the aim of achieving operational process simplification and cost reduction by merging 8+ legacy applications into one COTS product.
- Role Executed tests in various test phases E2E, SIT, ST

Python Scripting, Django, Django Rest Framework, Selenium SOAP, REST API Testing Using SOAP UI and Postman JIRA, HP-ALM Git, GitHub

2019 **TESTA, The European Software Testing Awards**

• Category: Best Overall Testing Project (Communications)

2019 ACE(Associates Consistently Excel), Tech Mahindra

2018 Bravo, Tech Mahindra

• Maximum number of defect logging, test execution and training newcomers.

COURSES

Complete Python 3.x, Udemy

Python Django - The Practical Guide, Udemy

Complete PL/SQL: "Beginner to Advanced", Udemy

WebServices/Rest API testing with SOAPUI, Udemy

Selenium webdriver with Python, Udemy

EDUCATION

2011 – 2013 Mumbai University, Higher Secondary School Certificate (HSC)

Mumbai, India

2013 – 2016 St. Andrew's College of Arts, Science and Commerce, Mumbai, India Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

E CERTIFICATES

PL/SQL 2 Python 2

Full Python course

INTERESTS

Cooking PC-Gaming

Expert level 😉

W LANGUAGES

English
 Hindi
 Marathi